<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hugo Test</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/</link><description>Recent content on Hugo Test</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>fr-fr</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Color Theme Switcher</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/theme-switcher/color-theme-switcher/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/theme-switcher/color-theme-switcher/</guid><description>Last year, the design gods decided that dark modes were the new hotness. "Light colors are for suckers", they laughed, drinking matcha tea on their fixie bikes or whatever.
And so every operating system, app and even some websites (mine included) suddenly had to come up with a dark mode. Fortunately though, this coincided nicely with widespread support for CSS custom properties and the introduction of a new prefers-color-scheme media query.</description></item><item><title>Basic HTML Elements</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/basic-elements/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/basic-elements/</guid><description>&lt;p>The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MathJax</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/mathjax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/mathjax/</guid><description>&lt;p>MathJax JavaScript library allows you to include mathematics in your web pages for viewing in any modern browser.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Translation Support</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/translation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/translation/</guid><description>&lt;p>With Hugo i18n possibilities, you can easily have a website in your language. This Hugo theme is ready to be translated into other languages. You can create a special file that contains translated text to show the visitor instead of English.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Featured Images</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/featured-images/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/featured-images/</guid><description>&lt;p>Featured image is the image that appears on summaries at the list pages and the top of content pages. Every content page&lt;br />
in this theme can have a featured image.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Hugo</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/getting-strated-with-hugo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/getting-strated-with-hugo/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Syntax Highlighting</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/syntax-highlighting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/syntax-highlighting/</guid><description>&lt;p>You can have code snippets highlighted so that they are easier to read on your site using Chroma, Hugo&amp;rsquo;s default syntax highlighter. It is built in Go lang and is really, really fast – and for the most important parts compatible with Pygments. Chroma takes source code and other structured text and converts it into syntax highlighted HTML, ANSI-coloured text, etc.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creating a New Theme</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/goisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/goisforlovers/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo uses the excellent &lt;a href="https://golang.org/">Go&lt;/a> &lt;a href="https://golang.org/pkg/html/template/">html/template&lt;/a> library for&lt;br />
its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very&lt;br />
small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of&lt;br />
logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other&lt;br />
template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of&lt;br />
similarities in Go templates.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Hugo</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/hugoisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/news/hugoisforlovers/</guid><description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the
appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site
you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313 Corresponding pseudo commands:</description></item><item><title>Cémoi</title><link>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polarhardboiled.github.io/hugotest/contact/</guid><description>My name is The Dude. I have the following qualities:
I rock a great beard I’m extremely loyal to my friends I like bowling That rug really tied the room together.
my history
To be honest, I’m having some trouble remembering right now, so why don’t you just watch my movie and it will answer all your questions.</description></item></channel></rss>